# Pranjali Gaonkar

London, United Kingdom - +44 74 35 508 504 pranjaligaonkar@gmail.com - LinkedIn

#### **SUMMARY**

A budding marketer, creative thinker, and strategic planner. Completed Masters in Strategic Marketing at the University of Greenwich and obtained a bachelor's degree in media and specialized in Advertising. Skilled in content creation and marketing research for digital mediums. Highly motivated to embrace any challenges and a firm believer in continuous learning. Enthusiastic to work individually or in a team to produce the desired result. I look forward to enhancing my knowledge and skills by working for a marketing organization with a complex management structure to upgrade my management skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Junior Researcher

September 2022 - Present (London)

## Bonhill Intelligence

- Carried out a variety of tasks and duties to support the research function, the research is focused on financial services and
  includes tracking forward looking investment strategies of fund selectors across the globe; handling historic fund flow data;
  and, compiling extensive ESG data in terms of tracking which funds are rated ESG compliant across some of the major ESG
  rating agencies.
- Ensured the report is accurate by carefully reviewing it and discussing it with other departments.
- Build relationships by coordinating with the local agencies to present the key data.
- · Liaised with the auditors to measure the team performance consistently.
- · Created surveys and email campaigns to boost the participation of the new customers.

# **Customer Sales Assistant** (London)

June 2022 - September 2022

#### Bershka

- Supervised the cash desk within a timely manner and provided financial reports to the managers.
- Investigated and resolved customer discrepancies aligned with the management and provided an 85% satisfaction rate.
- Supervised the incoming delivery and stock replenishment on the floor.
- Identified and implemented promotional offers for products eventually leading to an upsell.

#### Sales/Admission Assistant

August 2020 - December 2020

Skillsoft Overseas Education, Mumbai

- · Managed a detailed student database and ensured that the data was updated and kept secured.
- Catered to the student queries through emails and telephonic conversations. Supported students who did not have English as their first language and required special assistance.
- Guided the students with the application process of applying to British universities and assisted them in collating their documents for the application.

#### **Junior Marketing Assistant**

**January 2020 - August 2020** 

GlobalSkill App, Mumbai

- Designed the creative assets for the products involving multiple creative elements.
- Successfully pitched multi-channel marketing strategy to various sponsors.

#### Correspondent

January 2019- December 2019

Adgully Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

- · Responsible for handling social media content for the company on various platforms for event promotions.
- Achieved 10% more traffic on media platforms by strategizing SEO techniques.
- Responsible for writing creative content for the company and engaging various customers.
- · Handled the timely release of the press.
- Managed and released the transcribes of the video and the audio files.

## **EDUCATION**

## **MA Strategic Marketing**

September 2021 - September 2022 (London)

University of Greenwich, London

Distinction

**BA Mass Media** 

September 2017 - September 2020 (Mumbai

Mumbai University, Mumbai

First Class Degree

#### **CERTIFICATION**

Creative Certification Exam March 2023 (London)

Google Digital Academy

Google Ads Creative Certification March 2023 (London)

Google Digital Academy

Google Ads Search Certification March 2023 (London)

Google Digital Academy

Google Analytics for Beginners Certificate August 2022 (London)

Google

MILT Leadership Certificate November 2018 (Mumbai)

MILT Training Foundation

# **SKILLS**

# **Marketing Skills**

Analytics Customer Research Market Research
Content Creation Customer Segmentation Presentation
Content Management Database Management Social Media
Copywriting GDPR Storytelling
Customer Relationship Management Lead Nurturing

# Interpersonal skills

Public SpeakingTeamworkDecision MakingManagementCommunicationTime ManagementTeam LeadershipCustomer ServiceCritical Thinking

Conflict Management

## **Tools and Technologies**

Adobe Creative CloudMicrosoft ExcelSPSS StatisticsAdobe IllustratorMicrosoft Office SuiteTableauAdobe PhotoshopMicrosoft PowerPointMicrosoft Word